ILR School Office of Resident Instruction Sample MILR Examination /4031
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Office of Resident Instruction Sample MILR Examination
1959-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4031
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Sample comprehensive examinations for the Master of Industrial and Labor Relations (MILR) degree, 1960 to 1969.
7952307
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 02, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of sample comprehensive examinations for the Master of Industrial and Labor Relations (MILR) degree at the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1960 to 1969. The collection is arranged in chronological order.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3012: Alice Cook Papers /4004: ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4169: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4210: Frank B. Miller Files /4259: Frank B. Miller Corning Glass files /4308m: Frank Miller ILR School Poetry /4311: Frank Miller Papers
Education, Higher; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Office of Resident Instruction; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
7952307
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  May 9, 1960
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  January 5, 1961
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  May 26, 1961
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  January 9, 1962
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  May 14 and May 15, 1962
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  January 8, 1963
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  May 15, 1963
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  January 6, 1964
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  May 1964
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  January 4, 1965
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  May 11, 1966
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  December 1967
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- MILR comprehensive exam, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)